One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
I grabbed hold, digging in my claws
te ni totte tsume o tateta
but the future
sono mirai wa
blurred together, colors running
nijimu iro ni kasunde mieta
A red that can swallow even summer's hues
natsu no iro mo nuritsubusu you na aka ni
bokura no koe kakikesareteiku you de
now attempts to blot out our voices
Move those halting feet of yours
tachidomaru sono ashi o fumidasou ze
Don't let stand the lies for show
misekake no uso yarisugosu yori
I'll give up countless mornings for my vows
nandome no asa chikai to hikikaeru yo
For the dream that we shared
bokura ga miteita yume
Interception
Well, Stella,
you can’t just start talking out of nowhere.
Hmm? What do you mean, Shaka?
People will need to be
prepared to listen to you, surely.
What? What’s going on?
You really think that’s necessary...?
Some intelligence agency will pick this up,
and by the next day it’ll have
spread around the world...
Are you certain about that?
What if they manipulate the information?
You do have a point...
So what do we do, then?
Using the Navy branches all over the world
as relays,
we’ll force them to broadcast us over the brainwaves at maximum output.
The hell is this?!
Where’s this signal coming from?!
Through all Snails, sir! Fleet-wide!
Kill that signal!
Kill it now!
B-But...
...I can’t, sir!
Transponder Snails will be able to
receive audio signals,
but setting up the Video Transponder Snails
may take some time...
I suggest a wait time of one hour.
What is it you intend to
tell the world, Vegapunk...?
An hour?!
That seems long! So long, in fact...
Hey, yo, isn’t this...?
It’s Vegapunk, right?
From where, though?
And why now?
Fire!
...that it will give those who do not want
this message to be heard
the time to sabotage it.
All right, very well!
Let’s make the prep time
for receiving our message...
...ten minutes!
You hear that, world?!
Hey! Why am I hearing your voice,
Vegapunk?!
Holy Land
Mary Geoise
What is this broadcast-eh?!
What is going on-eh?!
Hey, Saturn...
What happened to Vegapunk?
Kizaru killed him.
He should be dead.
Ah...
That is what I believe.
I watched him die.
Did he arrange for this message
to transmit upon his death?
It would appear so...
What he will say, however,
is unknown to us...
If only we could find
the source of the broadcast...
It cannot be anywhere else
but the Labophase on Egghead.
It is currently protected by the barrier...
So, nine and a half minutes of waiting...
Want to invent something in the meantime?
I’m rather busy.
Why not have some coffee?
Dressrosa
New World
Hey, did you hear?!
This is huge!
The Dr. Vegapunk
is trying to tell the entire world something!
What?!
Bring the Video Transponder Snail!
Set up the screen!
This way, move it! We don’t have time!
Calculating probability of
signal jamming...
Rebecca, the picture’s coming in now.
That’s...
...Vegapunk?
Leo! Kabu!
Are you here to watch the broadcast?
Dat da pwofessor
Luffyland tooked hostage?!
What’s goin’ on over dere?
Huh?
Oh, Leo...
You really believe that bad press about Lucy?
Windmill Village
East Blue
The heck? I thought the news was about
Luffy being up to no good again.
Too bad we don’t have
a Video Transponder Snail...
Can’t we get one for the village,
Mayor? Pretty please?
And who’s gonna pay for it?!
Just raisin’ those things costs money, you know!
Long’s we got sound, that’s plenty!
Awwwwh!
Water Seven
Grand Line
Wake up!
This is serious!
Hrmm...
Alice...
Yes, President.
Set up the Video Transponder Snail
right away.
Already receiving in the next room, sir.
Iceberg's secretary
Alice
You’re ahead of the game, as usual...
It may be the middle of the night,
but given the apparent importance of this event,
I’ve delegated contact of all residents
so they can be ready to watch within ten minutes.
Anything else?
World Economic
Journal
What the?!
What’s this video about?!
It’s being relayed via Navy branches,
but it’s an independent signal!
What do you mean?
Then where are Luffy-san and the others now?
Look at the clock behind them, ya dunce.
That ain’t the current time on Egghead.
This footage is previously recorded!
It should be the scene of an inferno by now,
courtesy of a Buster Call!
West Blue
Is this the real Dr. Vegapunk?!
I heard his mind’s so sharp,
it cut its way out of his head!
North Blue
The man with the biggest brain in the world,
who brought light to us all...
South Blue
What’s so important that
he’s gotta tell the whole world?!
Maybe it’s the greatest invention of
the century?
Kamabakka Queendom
It’ll take ten minutes to brew the coffee.
I won’t have time to drink it!
Hmmm, hmmm...
The probability of signal jamming
is extremely low.
What is Vegapunk doing?!
But more importantly,
his head!
His mind’s gotten too sharp for it!
He’s the Doctor Vegapunk
I’ve heard lots about
who multiplied himself?!
I thought he was being held hostage!
He can do this in the middle of
that kind of situation?
I suspect...
...that my death is imminent.
Egghead
North-western side
Almost there!
I’ve spotted it!
Yeah, that’s right!
That’s our ship!
The Great Erik!
Vegapunk and the others...
Wonder if they’re doing okay...
Punchin’ ya ain’t doin’ squat, huh?
As long as any of my crew
are still on the island...
You guys ain’t goin’ nowhere!
Gum-Gum...
...Dawn...
...Cymbal!
If yer just gonna keep comin’ back
from whatever I do to ya...
How ‘bout I just...
...send ya flyin’, one-way!
There’s something in the air...
Incoming!
Whaaaa?!
Why’s nothin’ I’m doin’ hurtin’ him?!
Go away!
Kizaru, sir?
What just happened...?
Are you okay, sir?!
Admiral!
We do not have time, Saturn!
Vegapunk must not...
...be given license to speak!
Oh, that was close!
Whoa! Yikes! Eek!
Oof... Hup!
I shall make the summons.
Very good.
Huh?! What is...?
Black lightning?!
What’s that?!
That’s exactly like
when the Spider Geezer emerged...!
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop beep-beep-beep-bup-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipii pipopii, pipopiipii
Beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop, beep-bup-beep, bup-bip-bop
Piipapii papipo, piipapii papipo piipapii papipo, piipapii
Beep-bup-beep
Piipapii papipo, piipapii
No No No No No norenai
No, no, no, no, no, not feelin' it
kobiritsuichatte mou odorenai
I'm all stiff, all outta dances
My head feels so good, 'f I get unlucky again
atama Feel so good, mata Unlucky demo
Cola de fukitobase yowaki o
just gonna blow away the shy with a cola
Hey all you boys & girls! Looking good!
soko no Boys & Girls! omae ii yatsu
Hey all you boys & girls!
soko no Boys & Girls!
Update failed. I've had enough!
appudeto wa shippai kori gori
Wasn't it OK 'til yesterday?
kinou made nara seikai?
La la la la la la, run, run, run...
ran ran ran ran ran ran Run Run Run
"Hiding yet?"
mou ii kai?
You ready yet, up for a dance
junbi wa douyo odoreru no?
bukkowareteru kono jidai
in this broken era?
"Come find us!"
mou ii yo!
Spread out from here, drop into the world
koko kara kakusan sekai e Drop
Let loose on the stage of freedom and liberation
jiyuu to kaihou no Stage e
Those rising heads're punks!!!!!! No way!!!
wakiagaru atama ga Punk!!!!!! No way!!!
Sick of waitin', goof off and dance
matenaiyo fuzaketa Dance
Dopamine spilling over
afuredasu dopamin
The lonely singing in unity
kodoku ga tsudoi utau koushin
Bip-bip-bip-bup-bup-bup-bup-bupping
pipipi papapapapatteru
Can't can't can't count me out yet
mada mada mada horobinai
There's some stranger waving me over
shiranai dareka ga temaneki da
Smilin' so wide that it can't be real
uso mitai ni waratteru